apkmody.io 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy - APKMody

APKMody’s mission is to build the best and most enjoyable playground for all of you. And to do that, we have to understand you and show you what you want in a variety of ways, including the collection and use of your personal information.

What you are reading will give you information about how we collect, use, disclose and transfer, including your personal information. Because this information is related to the law, it seems they are quite difficult to understand and we will try to explain everything in the most easily understood. We welcome your comments and feedback on this Privacy Policy.

## The information we collect

As soon as you join the playground called APKMody, we receive and collect information about you. This work is ongoing as you play on our playground.

### Your registration information

When you register or use APKMody, you provide us with certain information voluntarily. This includes your display name, email address, avatar, comment and any other information you provide us.

### Your content

It is obvious that we are required to collect the content you submit to APKMody, then our system will transform them into the most interesting spiritual food you make for others in this playground. Include articles, comments, reviews …

If you post pictures on the website, you should avoid posting images containing your location information (EXIF GPS). We do not use this information and have a mechanism for automatically removing them before public display for your safety. But we still recommend that you take care.

### Cookie

We also use “cookies” (small text files sent by your computer every time you visit our site, unique to your APKMody account or browser) or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies or other similar technologies, we use session cookies (until you close the browser) or persistent cookies (until you or your browser delete them). For example, we use cookies to store your language preferences or other settings so that you do not have to set them every time you visit APKMody. Some of the cookies we use are linked to your APKMody account (including information about you, such as the email address you provided us), and other cookies do not.

### Your IP and your user agent string

Your IP address and user agent are logged every time you visit this website.

## How we use your information

We will explain in detail how your information is used.

It is our responsibility to ensure the safety of your information, your privacy by keeping the system secure, secure and always have backup solutions.

We will store your information until APKMody is no longer active, or when you request to remove your own information from our system.

What we collect from you will be provided, analyzed, managed, improved and personalized to:

### Keep the system stable

Obviously, we always have to keep this playground stable. There are a lot of people involved and we do not want this playground to have any problems. Therefore, we will identify, investigate and prosecute with prohibited, fraudulent or illegal activities.

Information also helps us detect better spam and prevent bad behavior before it’s done.

### Keeping you always satisfied about us

You will not have to take the language or log in every time you visit this website. By using the information you provide, we can determine your personal preferences, geographic location, … to show you what you want and most relevant to you.

### Keep communicating with you through the contact method you provide

Sometimes we would like to send you some small suggestions, or some announcements, or other things related to our service. By using your contact information, we will be able to easily connect with you, as well as receive personalized suggestions yourself.

### Compliance with the decision, legal requirements from a management level, governmental agency of any country

We do not share and will never share your information with any other 3rd parties. Although we are comfortable on the playground, it does not mean that we are left with your privacy.

## Your right

If you have an account at APKMody, you can edit any information we store such as email, display name, password and similar information.

You do not have to use your real name when joining APKMody, we respect your privacy and anonymity.

You also have the right to request that we remove any information about you.

## Changes to this privacy policy

There is nothing eternal. And this privacy policy too. So we may have some changes to this document over time. When we make changes to the terms of our privacy policy that we consider important, we will let you know via the service or by email. By continuing to use our services after the changes have been made, you agree to accept the changes.

APKMody’s journey continues with your companionship. And although APKMody is extremely simple, humorous, we are always serious about the privacy and personal information of anyone.

 _Effective Date: November 12, 2018  
Last updated: November 12, 2018_
